Pina Gomet

113 Pegasus Dr, Groton, CT 06340 (860) 899 7108 | pina.gomet@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Sales professional seeking technical pre-sales position. Excellent verbal and written communication skills, as well as over 5 years of retail sales experience. Active learner of technology who is passionate about how technology integrations can drive digital transformation at businesses.

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut, College of Liberal Arts and Sciences

Graduated December 2021

B.A. in Communication

<u>Relevant Coursework:</u> Multimedia Storytelling; Presenting in Digital World; Statistics; Research Methods in Communication; Opportunity Generation, Assessment, and Promotion; Economics; Persuasion

UCONN Coding Bootcamp

Expected Completion Aug. 2022

Bootcamp to learn REST development, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, Git, and more

University of Michigan

Completed February 28, 2022

Programming for Everybody (Python)

Coursera Project Network

Completed February 22, 2022

Introduction to CRM

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lowes Aug. 2021 - Present Sales Associate Waterford, CT

- Provided thoughtful recommendations to customers by matching products to expressed pain points realized sales of 30 units/day
- Maintained up-to-date knowledge on 30+ item product catalog by regularly reviewing new documentation
- Managed inventory through digital record-keeping and coordinated with corresponding departments when inventory was low

CoachJan. 2020 - May 2021Sales AssociateMashantucket, CT

Sales Associate Mashantucket,

- Collaborated with other associates and managers to provide product information and outstanding service to customers
 Surpassed daily sales goals by 100% consistently through strategic cross-sell and promotion of Coach products
- Enabled customers on digital assistant tool that connected users to personalized online shopping experiences
- Analyzed sales activity by assessing customer feedback and purchase history data increased customer satisfaction regularly

AéropostaleMay 2017 - May 2019Sales AssociateFarmington, CT

- · Guided an average of 25 customers/day by responding to inquiries and locating relevant products
- Trained all new sales employees on effective sales, service, and operational strategies to maximize team performance

LEADERSHIP

UCONNN's Thai, Lao, Cambodian Student Association

Storrs, CT

Secretary

Sept. 2019 – May 2021

- Co-led transition to a successful all-digital environment when student life became 100% remote due to the COVID-19 pandemic accomplished this by standing up multiple software tools and applications under a unified operating model
- Managed social media relations through Facebook, Instagram, and Discord increased following and engagement

Women in Business Storrs, CT

Membership Engagement

Sept. 2020 – May 2021

· Planned events and encouraged regular feedback from club members to inform activities and improve member involvement

PROJECTS

 JobSwipe
 Storrs, CT

 Creator & Lead
 Sept. 2020 – Dec. 2021

• Produced hypotheses, conducted research, defined use cases, and diagrammed technology systems to iterate proposal for a job matching app with a simple swipe-based user interface

SKILLS

Software: Microsoft Office, Python, CRM, Final Cut Pro, iMovie, Vegas Pro

Soft Skills: Sales Expertise, Negotiation Tactics, Problem-Solving, Organization, Written & Oral Communication

Languages: Thai (Beginner), Lao (Beginner)